A Guide to the Papers of Murrell Edmunds, 1935-1960 and n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Murrell Edmunds 1935-1960 and n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
5989-b
This collection consists of 14 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift of Murrell Edmunds on 9 March 1959.
Contents List
- Richard Keller to Hardy Kreeger (circular letter concerning Sojourn Among Shadows). 1935 December 11, TLS. 1 p
- Ben Belitt to Murrell Edmunds 1937 June 7, TLS. 2 p
- Elliott B. Macrae to Murrell Edmunds, (concerning a volume of short stories). 1944 November 30, TLS. 1 p
- "The Pass," (a chapter written by Murrell Edmunds for a volleyball manual edited by Edmund Welch). Mimegraphed typescript with autograph notes. [1956], 5 [p]
- Merrill Pollack to Murrell Edmunds. 1960 February 17, TLS. 1 p
- Murrell Edmunds to Merrill Pollack. 1960 February 28, TL (copy). 1 p
- Lincoln Colcord to Murrell Edmunds [?] Sunday, ALS. 4 p. on l l.
- Beautiful Upon The Mountains(novel) n. d., typescript material discarded during revision. [29] p.
- Behold, Thy Brother(novel) n. d., typescript with autograph changes. [29] p. unbound. (on yellow pulp paper).
- Behold, Thy Brother(novel) n. d., typescript (printer's copy) with autograph corrections. 59 p. and [4] p., unbound.
- "First Circus" (short story) n. d., typescript with autograph changes. Signed. [10] p.
- "Footsteps Down The Hall" (short story). n. d., typescript with autograph changes. [23] p.
- "How the Devil Came To Bald Ridge" (short story) n. d., typescript with autograph changes. 12 p.
- "Moon of My Delight" (3-act play) n. d., typescript list of revisions. [12] p.